McKersie, Robert B. Arbitration, Civil Rights, and Interrogation Files 6958
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert B. McKersie Arbitration Civil Rights, and Interrogation Files
1958-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McKersie, Robert B.
6958
7.61 cubic feet
7.6 linear ft.
Arbitration awards, papers (documents), publications.
This is a collection of arbitration, civil rights and interrogation cases.
10003298
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, October 01, 2019
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, October 11, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Robert B. McKersie, DBA
Professor of Management, Emeritus, Sloan School of Management, Massachusetts Institute of Technology
Robert McKersie is professor emeritus of management at the MIT Sloan School of Management, where he has been since 1980. Prior to his time at MIT, he served as dean of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, and as a faculty member of the Graduate School of Business at the University of Chicago. McKersie has served on several presidential commissions at the national level, is a member of the National Academy of Arbitrators, and was president of the National Industrial Relations Research Association (now the Labor and Employment Relations Association). He is the author of numerous articles relating to human resources, industrial relations, and operations management.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4033: Robert B. McKersie Files /4071: Robert B. McKersie Additional Files /4142: Robert B. McKersie Additional Papers /4284: Robert B. McKersie Additional Papers /4343: Robert B. McKersie Collections 5004: AAA Arbitration in Government 5119: AAA Voluntary Labor Arbitration Tribunal Case Files 6145 AV: AAA Audio Recording 6213: Robert B. McKersie Additional Files 6325: Robert B. McKersie PIE Trucking Company Files 6326: Robert B. McKersie Research Collection for "The Impact of Collective Bargaining on Management" 6327: Robert B. McKersie Nassau County Multi-Municipality Productivity Project Files 6448: American Arbitration Association Collections 6958 AV: Robert B. McKersie Arbitration, Civil Rights, and Interrogation Audio-Visual Materials 6960: Speeches of William N. Margolis, Assistant Director of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service
Labor arbitration; Civil rights movement; Interrogation; Educing information; McKersie, Robert B.; American Arbitration Association (AAA); Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service (FMCS); Information Science Board (ISB); New York State Public Employment Relations Board (NYS PERB)
10003298
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 51-30-0004-68, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 51-30-0191-69, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 51-30-0462-70, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Arbitration N45 Mediation Board Case No. A72-137, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Arbitration United Steel Workers, Local 14795, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. A74-40, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 15-30-0184-74, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 15-39-0266-76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. A77-42, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 15-39-0109-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. A77-199, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 15-39-0051-77, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Arbitration IAM, Local 1607, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 15-30-0160-78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Arbitration NYS Mediation Board Case No. A77-1183, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. A78-164, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-0027-80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-1443-79, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 15-67-0121-80, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-1082-80, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-2290-80, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-0160-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1244-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-0947-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1325-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1325-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-0313-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-0915-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1570-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Arbitration AAA Case no. 1130-1438-81, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-1156-81, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Arbitration Teamsters Local No. 25, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-2443-81, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-2270-81, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-2536-81, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-0521-81, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-0970-82, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Arbitration IBEW, Local 827, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-023-83, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. A82-352, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Arbitration PERB No. A82-129, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Arbitration FMCS Case. Communications Workers of America, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1418-83, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Arbitration Utilities Workers Union of America, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-2298-83, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1493-83, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. 85-128, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. A84-261, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-1507-84, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1139-0522-85, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Arbitration Case No. 86K/05626, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-0600-86, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-2373-86, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Arbitration Local 105, IBEW, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1048-87, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-1643-87, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Arbitration PERB Case No. NYS/82:87-136-D, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Arbitration MA Case No. 88-06605, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Arbitration MA Case No. 88-14264, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 1130-0980-88, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 90-00400, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Arbitration AAA Case no. 11-390-00522-40, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00371-92, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Arbitration AAA East No. 11-300-00043-92, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-00980-92, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-02036-92, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Arbitration Case No. 95-18140, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 97-07610, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Arbitration OER Case No. 95-1012, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Arbitration OER Case No. 96-0632, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-02339-97, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Arbitration OER Case No. 94-0366, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Arbitration MA Case No. 2648, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-00640-99, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-01537-99, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Arbitration OER 99-12-196, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 030129-05309-8, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Arbitration Lakeview Firefighters Association Local 3188, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-01193-03, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 04-03245, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-01128-04, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 04-02620-A, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00936-04, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00936-04 (Folder 1 of 2), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00936-04 (Folder 2 of 2), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 04-582556-A, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 04-07006, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Arbitration Huhtamaki, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 040721-07006-7, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-02626-04, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Arbitration MREP Case No. 202, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-00788-05, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00893-04, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Arbitration United Airlines, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-00808-03 (Folder 1 of 2), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-00508-03 (Folder 2 of 2), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-00788-05 (Folder 1 of 2), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-300-00788-05 (Folder 2 of 2), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Arbitration Grievance No. 03-I13701 (Folder 1 of 3), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Grievance No. I13701 (Folder 2 of 3), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Grievance No. I13701 (Folder 3 of 3), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00944-06, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Arbitration FMCS Case No. 07-02195-1, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00253-08, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11 390 02188 07, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-02458-09, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Arbitration OCB Case No. A-13485-10, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Arbitration OCB Case No. A-13770-11, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Arbitration OCB Case No. 47679, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Arbitration OCB Case No. A-13967-11, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Arbitration OCB Case No. A-14109-13, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Arbitration OCB Case No. A-14072-11, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-01972-12, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-01400-12, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-01171-12, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Arbitration AAA Case No. 11-390-00851-13, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Arbitration District Council 37, Local 1070 (Folder 2 of 3), 2014 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Arbitration District Council 37, Local 1070 (Folder 1 of 3), 2014 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Arbitration District Council 37, Local 1070 (Folder 3 of 3), 2014 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Arbitration Insurance Workers International Union (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Scope and Contents
  No Date
- Arbitration Lynn Police Association (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Arbitration Correspondence Regarding Working as an Arbiter in Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts Board of Conciliation and Arbitration, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts Joint Labor-Management Committee for Municipal Police and Fire, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- NYS Continuity of Employment Committee Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  April 1, 1976 to March 31, 1977
- Analysis of the Lay Off Experience and Review of Lay Off Procedures in New York State, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Continuity of Employment Committee Report, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Transition of State Employment From DMH Institutional Care Units to Community Care Units, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- The Utica/Marcy Consolidation: Findings and Recommendations, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- A Cost-Benefit Balance Sheet for Evaluating Layoffs as a Policy Strategy, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- State Wide Survey, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Change and Continuity, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- The Closing of Urban State Agencies: Impact on Employee Attitudes, Perceptions, Careers, and Economic Security (Box 2, Folder 35)
- The Governance Transfer Program: Issues and Operations (Box 2, Folder 36)
- The Relocation of a Rural Hospital Unit: The Impact of Rumors and Ambiguity on Employees (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Continuity of Employment Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Donald Wollett's Book Notes and Correspondences, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- First Unitarian Church, Chicago IL, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Reverend Jack Kent Correspondence, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Buds of a Feather (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Alex Poinsett, 1965-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Alex Poinsett: 5 "Ws" and an "H" (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Alex Poinsett: 5 "Ws" and an "H" (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Betty Sykes (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Commission on Social Responsibilities, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Chicago Area Council of Liberal Churches, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Norma Poinsett on Unitarian Universalism, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Wanted: More Negro Apprentices at Washburne Trade School, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Making Contact with the Chicago Labor Scene (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Blacks in Unions (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Black Dissident and Black Caucus (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Black Dissident and Black Caucus (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 15)
- The Negro Worker In the Black Labor Market, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- The Employment Front (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Rangers Business Institute (RBI) (Box 3, Folder 18)
- How I Almost Got To Washington (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Offices of Minority Enterprise (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Equal Employment Opportunity in the United States in the 1960s (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Yale Brozen Correspondence, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Putting Our Best Foot Forward (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Maurice H. Stans Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Motorola Project, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- George J. Yoxall Correspondence, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Interview with Tim Black, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Timuel Black (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Seth Patner Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Notes on Interview with Ron Gryzwinski (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Woodlawn/University of Chicago, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Impressions of a Freedom March (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Interview with Paul Goldstein (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Tenant Unions (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Operation Breadbasket (Folder 1 of 2), 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Operation Breadbasket (Folder 2 of 2), 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- D.E. Josephs: Operation Breadbasket and Jewel: A Progress Report, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- The Council of Hyde Park and Kenwood Churches and Synagogues, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Neighborhood Care (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Interviews (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Joan Powers Correspondences, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Martin Luther King, JR (Box 3, Folder 42)
- AD6 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Manuscript Reference Materials (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Back-Up Notes (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Manuscript Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Manuscript Drafts (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Manuscript Drafts (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Memo from the Social Action Committee, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Manuscript Draft Pages (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Manuscript Draft Pages Re-ordered (Folder 1 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Pp. 1-77
- Manuscript Draft Pages Re-Orders (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Pp. 78-189
- Manuscript Draft Pages Re-Ordered (Folder 3 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Pp. 190-314
- Manuscript Draft Pages Re-ordered (Folder 4 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Pp. 315-386
- Photos and Captions (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Active Photo File (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Backup Photo File (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Permissions for Photos for Manuscripts, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Maps of Chicago and Hyde Park (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Letters for Quotes in the Chapters (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Quoted Materials Permissions, 2002-2012 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Reader Comments and Publisher Guidelines (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Southern Illinois University Parts, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Book Notes (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Hotpointe File (Box 4, Folder 16)
- The Chicago Crime Scenes Project (Box 4, Folder 17)
- The March of Time (Box 4, Folder 18)
- ILR School Affirmative Action Program, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Negotiations in Other Settings (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Trotsky, Rivera, Kahlo Article, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Office of Federal Contract Compliance (OFCC), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Race Panel Notes and Correspondences, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Race Panel Background Information (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Community Organizing (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Robert McKersie: Affirmative Action and the Employment Position of Minorities, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- George F. Travers and Robert B. McKersie: An Analysis of Negro Occupation Position, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Barriers to Work Place Advancement Experienced by African Americans, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Phyllis A. Wallace: Black Women in the Labor Force, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- George W. Bradshaw: The Black Worker: A Study of the Black Labor Movement in Chicago (Box 4, Folder 30)
- The Chicago Plan (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Notes on the "Chicago Plan" (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Jeffrey M. Greene: Comment on Black Dissidents, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- J.A. Blanchard: Continental Casualty Company Medicare Department (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Donald E. Mulcahy: The Continuing Quest for Equal Schools (Box 4, Folder 35)
- W. Ellison Chalmers and Gerald W. Cormick: Collective Bargaining in Racial Disputes?, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Jeffrey M. Greene: Dissident Worker Groups - A Management View, A Second Look, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Economic Development of the Ghetto: A Matrix of Problem Areas and Program Responses (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Robert B. McKersie: The Economic Health of the South Side and the University of Chicago (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Equal Employment Opportunities Commission (EEOC) Papers (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Robert B. McKersie: Entrepreneurship and Black Economic Development (Box 4, Folder 41)
- George F. Travers, Jr.: Factors Affecting the Structure of Minority Occupation Position (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Garvin-Allyn Company (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Barrack Obama, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- This is the shot made for the (?)/McFadde (handwritten label, difficult to read), CD/DVD (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Ghetto Multipliers: A Case Study of Hough, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- George P. Shultz: How a Republican Desegregated the South's Schools, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Robert E. Weems and Lewis A. Randolph: The Ideological origins of Richard M. Nixon's "Black Capitalism" initiative (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Robert J. Havighurst: Importance of the Superintendent in the program for Integration, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Patrick D. Jones: The Selma of the North, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Making the Second Ghetto: A Neighborhood on a Hill (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Minority Employment Patterns In An Urban Labor Market: The Chicago Experience (Box 5, Folder 7)
- My Days With Harlem Barbeque Sauce (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Robert B. McKersie: Negro Entrepreneurship (Box 5, Folder 9)
- George F. Travers: Notes on the Probability of Integrated in a Labor Market of Fixed Total and Negro Size, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- PMD Windup Lecture (Box 5, Folder 11)
- The Problems of a Small Negro Businessman (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Robert B. McKersie and Werner Sengenberger: Program Planning Model: Version II (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Robert B. McKersie: Rapid Economic Advance Program (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Ray Marshall: Trends in Black Income and Employment, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- David Oser: Why ShoreBank Succeededand Why It Failed, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Henry Kalven Jr.: A Worth Tradition: Freedom of Speech in America, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Correspondences (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Handwritten notes (Box 5, Folder 19)
- News Clippings and Articles (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 20)
- News Clippings and Articles (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 21)
- News Clippings and Articles (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 22)
- David L. Shapiro: Negotiation Theory and Practice: Exploring Ideas to Aid Information Education, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Interrogator: Early Materials (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Entrepreneurship Seminar Board Notes, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Professor Watson and McKersie's Research Recommendations, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Recent HRW Work on the Torture and Abuse of U.S. Detainees, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Human Rights Watch
- Rolling Out the Theory, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Questions for Debriefing Interrogators in Foreign Countries, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Richard Walton: Educing Information from Detainees Introduction. Annotated Draft, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Richard Walton: Educing Interrogations From Detainees. Part I: Consideration in Planning Negotiations. Annotated Draft, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Richard Walton: Educing Interrogations from Detainees. Part II: Negotiating Strategies and Tactics. Annotated Draft, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Names of the Detained in Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Educing Information Professionals (EFPs), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Four Quadrant Grid, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Richard Walton: Educing Information from Detainees. Printing Draft Annotated, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Cambridge III Meeting Agenda, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Petula Dvorak: WWII Secret Interrogators Break Their Silence, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Deborah Nelson and Nick Turse: Army Knew About Torture in Vietnam, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Geneva Convention Relative to the Treatment of Prisoners of War, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Intelligence Science Board Study on Educing Information Proposed JMIC Thesis Topics Draft, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- An Israeli Perception on the Essence of Arabs, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Book Reviews, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Richard Walton: Educing Information From Detainees Introduction, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Richard Walton: Educing Information from Detainees. Part I: Consideration in Planning Negotiations, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Richard Walton: Educing Information from Detainees. Part II: Negotiating Strategies and Tactics, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Richard Walton: Educing Information from Detainees. Part III: The Engagement from Beginning to End, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Questions and Departures flagged in the Richard Walden Manuscript (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Still Struggling with this "Goal", 2006 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- "Case Discussion" Prisoner 140, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- 9/11 Mother Struggles to Understand Son's Killer, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- R. Jeffrey Smith: Behind the Debate, Controversial CIA Techniques, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Protocol for Interviewing EIP?, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Military Studies in the Jihad Against the Tyrants, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Case Studies: Vehicles (not content), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Intelligence Science Board: Study on Educing Information, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Material for the End Piece, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- "A Letter From Iraq", 2006 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Using Web Cameras, Laptop Computers, and the Performance Analysis Software to Teach Negotiation and Other Skills, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- RAR-102 with Professor Ernest May, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Blindspots II: The Interrogation Game, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Protocol Question, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- George Packer: Knowing the Enemy: Can Social Scientists Redefine the "War on Terror"?, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Educing Information Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Educing Information Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Study on Educing Information Draft, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- EI Biblio & Articles - 5/06, 2006; CD/DVD (Box 8, Folder 1)
- The Future of the Leverage Tables, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 2)